A Guide to the Marion Gandy Wyatt Papers 1919-1930
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
Marion Gandy Wyatt Papers 1919-1930
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
1919-1930
20 items
Photographs of Virginia State University buildings and students. Marion Wyatt was the daughter of John Gandy who was President of Virginia State. Acc. #1982-21
Marion Gandy Wyatt
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
A gift from Marion Gandy Wyatt in 1982.
Biographical/Historical Information
Marion Gandy Wyatt was born in 1906 on the campus of Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute in ettrick, Va. She was one of four children born to John and Carrie Gandy. Marion Gandy completed her secondary education in the schools located on campus and then matriculated at Fisk University.
Scope and Content Information
Photographs of the buildings and individuals who were at Virginia State University during Marion Gandy's early years growing up on the campus.
Series Description
Series I.Photographs Individuals, buildings and campus scenes from the time period 1919-1921.
Box List
- Photographs
  - Class of 1902 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Class of 1919 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Class of 1920 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Class of 1923 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Class of 1924 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Football 1901 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Tennis (Box-folder 1:7)
  - Male Tennis (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Old Virginia Hall 1901 (Box-folder 1:9)
  - Old Virginia Hall (Box-folder 1:10)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha 1920 (Box-folder 1:11)
  - Ex. Committee of the N.A.T. 1927 (Box-folder 1:12)
  - C.I.A.A., Coaches 1930 (Box-folder 1:13)
  - Male Faculty, V.S.U. (Box-folder 1:14)
  - Land Grant College Presidents (Box-folder 1:15)
  - John M. Gandy (Box-folder 1:16)
  - William Rogers (Box-folder 1:17)
  - Thomas Pawley (Box-folder 1:18)
  - John M. Gandy and others (Box-folder 1:19)
  - Wedding Picture Nov. 12, 1944 (Box-folder 1:20)